<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Getting Started with Aqua Platform on ps-eks-accelerator</title><link>https://jonahjon.github.io/ps-eks-accelerator/configure_aqua/</link><description>Recent content in Getting Started with Aqua Platform on ps-eks-accelerator</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 19:01:12 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jonahjon.github.io/ps-eks-accelerator/configure_aqua/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Installing pre-requisites</title><link>https://jonahjon.github.io/ps-eks-accelerator/configure_aqua/tools/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 19:01:12 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://jonahjon.github.io/ps-eks-accelerator/configure_aqua/tools/</guid><description>Installing eksctl for managing Amazon EKS curl --silent --location &amp;quot;https://github.com/weaveworks/eksctl/releases/latest/download/eksctl_$(uname -s)_amd64.tar.gz&amp;quot; | tar xz -C /tmp sudo mv /tmp/eksctl /usr/local/bin eksctl version Installing aquactl for managing Aqua operations The interactive Aqua Security aquactl command line tool simplifies the deployment of Aqua Platform on a variety of environments, including Amazon EKS.
wget &amp;quot;https://get.aquasec.com/aquactl/stable/aquactl&amp;quot; chmod +x ./aquactl ./aquactl --help</description></item><item><title>Creating an Amazon EKS cluster</title><link>https://jonahjon.github.io/ps-eks-accelerator/configure_aqua/eks_cluster/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 19:01:12 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://jonahjon.github.io/ps-eks-accelerator/configure_aqua/eks_cluster/</guid><description>Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS) is a fully managed Kubernetes service, trusted to run the most sensitive and mission critical applications because of its security, reliability, and scalability.
EKS Cluster creation eksctl create cluster --name aqua --region ${AWS_REGION} --zones ${AWS_REGION}a,${AWS_REGION}b Launching EKS and all the dependencies will take approximately 15 minutes
Verify the cluster Test the cluster: Confirm your nodes:
kubectl get nodes # if we see our 2 nodes, we know we have authenticated correctly Export the Worker Role Name for use throughout the workshop: STACK_NAME=$(eksctl get nodegroup --cluster aqua -o json | jq -r '.</description></item><item><title>Deploying Aqua Platform on Amazon EKS</title><link>https://jonahjon.github.io/ps-eks-accelerator/configure_aqua/deploy_aqua/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 19:01:12 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://jonahjon.github.io/ps-eks-accelerator/configure_aqua/deploy_aqua/</guid><description>You can deploy the Aqua Platform application in an existing Amazon EKS cluster in a separate namespace. For easier scaling and high-availability, deploy it in an Amazon EKS cluster of its own in a separate virtual private cloud (VPC).
Create an Amazon RDS Postgres database for Aqua Platform Aqua Platform requires a Postgres database to store operational data such as policies, configuration data, and audit events. To provision Amazon RDS with a PostgreSQL engine option, launch this AWS CloudFormation template inside your AWS account.</description></item><item><title>Configuring Enforcers for Aqua Platform</title><link>https://jonahjon.github.io/ps-eks-accelerator/configure_aqua/configure_enforcers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 19:01:12 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://jonahjon.github.io/ps-eks-accelerator/configure_aqua/configure_enforcers/</guid><description>Aqua takes a policy-driven approach to enforce security for remediation and compliance. To do this effectively, it uses Aqua Enforcers to monitor the runtime activity of containers, collect information about the running workloads, and enforce security based on the policies defined. Aqua provides various types of Enforcers tailored specifically to the different deployment environments.
Aqua Enforcers for Amazon EKS are deployed as a Kubernetes DaemonSet on every cluster worker node to be managed by Aqua.</description></item></channel></rss>